truiton.com 2014-11-23

# Privacy Policy - Truiton.com

**Truiton.com respects your privacy.**

We do not share personal information with third-parties nor do we store information we collect about your visit to this blog for use other than to analyze content performance through the use of cookies, which you can turn off at anytime by modifying your Internet browser’s settings. Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Truiton.com. We are not responsible for the republishing of the content found on this blog on other Web sites or media without our permission.  This privacy policy is subject to change without notice.

**Comments**

Comments are welcomed and encouraged on this site, but there are some instances where comments will be edited or deleted as follows:

  1. Comments deemed to be spam or questionable spam will be deleted. Including a link to relevant content is permitted, but comments should be relevant to the post topic.
  2. Comments including profanity will be deleted.
  3. Comments containing language or concepts that could be deemed offensive will be deleted.
  4. Comments that attack a person individually will be deleted.

The owner of this blog reserves the right to edit or delete any comments submitted to this blog without notice. This comment policy is subject to change at any time.

**Credit card details**

Truiton.com will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on Truiton.com. This credit card details policy is subject to change at any time.

**Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Truiton.com to recognize you each time you visit this site. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Truiton.com does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds, and ad networks.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Truiton.com and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Truiton.com have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information email [webmaster](mailto:mgupt@truiton.com).
